Finding Aid for the Memorial to WillHard Brownell Jewell
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Outgoing correspondence, 1927-1960, is arranged chronologically. Date and in parentheses, name of addressee are given for each letter.
  - 13 Jan. (Prof. A.F. Buddington; Tenn. Valley Auth.), 3 Feb. (Hr. Jack Richards), 13 Feb. (Central Natl, Trailways Bus(Service) System), 17 Feb. (Hiss Florence Eller - Central Natl. Trailways Bus Sys.; Mrs. Madeline Pond), 22 Feb. (Dr. F.H. Lahee), 9 March (Mr. Overton Williams), 16 March (Prof. A.F. Buddington\ The Hammer Blow Tool Co.; Hiss Laurs Louise Hart; J.H. Tull Hetals & Supply Co.; Mr. D.Q. Woodruff), 23 Harch (Hrs. Louise Russell Berryhill, Jr.; The Whitehead Hetal Products Co.), 30 Harch (Hr. E.E. Bryan; Prof. A.F. Bddington; J.H. Tull Hetal & Supply Co.), 5 April (Hiss Hary T. Baker; Dr. Richmond C. Beatty; Hr. W.C. Worthington), 20 April (Prof. T.G. Andrews; Champion Outboard Motors Co.; Eyinrude Moters; Johnson Motors; Kiehaefer Corp.; Martin Motors; Muncie Gear Works), 6 May (Mr. Robt. L. Straker), 7 May (Mr. Raymond F. Long),II May (Mr. D.E. Clark,; Hr. H.T. Giles), l8 June (Miss Mary Siler), 1948 (Box 1)
  - 15 Oct. (Hiss Roberta Hefley; Mr. E.V. Murphree), 16 Oct. (Hr. Roy Tasco cont. Davis; Mr. Hugh D. Miser), 19 Oct. (Mr. C. Doswell Olson), 21 Oct. Bausch & Lomb Optical Co.), 21 oct. (Mr. Stuart Delgado, Jr.; Eastman Kodak Co.; Mr. Gerald Henderson; Mr. D.W. Lackey; Mr. John S. Snyder; Miss Anna Burns Watkinp; Mr, Lewis F, Wood), 26 Oct. (Mr. Nicholas A. Rose), 28 Oct. (Mr. Overton Williams), 1 Nov. (Central Scientific Co.; Fisher Scientific Co.; %, Charles Silin), 5 Nov. (Mr. M. Hiller), 8 Nov. (Col. James 0. Brauer; Dr. Charles R.L. Oder; Mr. A.E. Sayles, Jr.), 12 Nov. (Mr. L.R. Collins), 3 Dec. (Mr. Ned Sayford), 11 Dec. (Mr. Will H. Shearon, Jr.), 16 Dec. (Consolidated Bus Co.), 1948 (Box 2)
  - 8 Jan. (Mr. M. Everett Corbett), 22 Jan. (Hr. Joe Booker; Hiss Laura Hart; Hr. Edward H. Morgan), 29 Jan. (Mr. W.P. Roe), 4 Feb. (Dean Meredith P. Crawford), 11 Feb. (Mr. Oliver W. Beinfohr; Dean Fred J. Lewis;,Prof. George W. White; Mr. Overton Williams), 25 r«b. (Pres. E.H. Elam -(Martin College); Dr. Harold R. Wanless), 4 March (Prof. Paris B. Stockdale), 12 March (BrsdJohn T. Bate), 17 March (Mr. Raoul C. Mitchell), 25 March (Hiss Laura Hart; Hrs. John H. Jewell; Hr. Nicholas J.A. Schreiber) HMMX S» 2 April (Hrs. John H. Jewell; Hr. Fred D. Love;), 8 April (Prof. John C. HcCampbell; Prof. R.A. Steinmayer), 15 April (Eastman Kodak Co.), 23 April ( Dr. A.F. Buddington), 1949 (Box 2)
  - 6 May (Southern Bell Telephone & telegraph Co.), 20 May (Mr. Elmer J. cont. Weems), 27 May (Mr. E.E. Bryan), 6 June (Asst. for.Htls. and Stockpile Policies; John Wiley and Sons, Inc.), 8 June (Mr. R.H. Whitney), 9 June (Dean Meredith P. Crawford), 15 July (Prof. Charles H. Behre, Jr.; Mr. P.C. Stoddart), 29 Sept. Chemical Rubber co.; 15 Oct. (Mr. Eugene Curtiss; Mr. Philip B. King;.Mr. Eric Seiler); 20 Oct. (Mr. D.M. Delo; Heinicke Instrum. Corp.; Mr. George Nilan), 27 Oct. (The Penny Hill Co.), 10 Nov. (Gamma Scientific Co; Technical Specialities Cp.), 3 Dec. (Mr. James B. Murray; Division of Geology and Geography - Natl. Research Council; Readers'Digest Assoc.; Tenn. Valley Auth.; Dr. Arthur B. Cleaves), 8 Dec. ( Mr. Brinkmann; Mr. Karl Lambrecht; Dr. S.W. Peterson; Survey Director, Care A.S.M.E.), 22 Dec. (Mr. Karl Lambrecht; Mr. Benton Mc-Keeham), 1949 (Box 2)
  - 5 Jan. (Mr. E.E. Curtiss), 12 Jan. (Mr. Benton McKeeham), 19 Jan. (Mr. Thomas C. Barr, Jr.; Mr. E.C. Roberts), 16 Feb. (Mr. Richard Stearns), 9 March (Dr. Paris B. Stockdale), 7 April (Commercial Letter Shop), 21 April (Mr. Scruggs), 27 April (Mr. E.V. Murphree), 4 May (Miss Louise B. Shaffer), 11 May (Bausch and Lomb Optical Co.; Mrs. Madeline Pond), 18 May (Mr. E.V. Murphree), 23 May (Readers' Digest) Time, Inc. ), 1 June (Mr. Billy Hunt; C.E. MacQuigg; Seismograph Service Corp.; Mr. Warren Sullivan), l8 Sept. (American Geological Inst.; Monsieur R. Laffitte), 5 Oct. (Mrs. Ed Wailey; Mr. John H. Webb), 11 Oct. (Mr. Troy L. Birdsong), 13 Oct. (McGraw-Hill Book Co., Inc.), 19 Oct. (Mr. N.A. Rpse), 26 Oct. (Ginn and Company; Dr. F.C. Kruger; Mr. Guy Stack; Profs. Warren Mae Deacon, Merlin D. Peterson, and Wlm. Binkley), 2 Nov. (Dr. Fredrick C. Kruger), 16 Nov. (Dr. Sam Shoup), 17 Nov. (Mr. Eugene Curtiss; Mrs. Bennie T. Hahn; Dr. Carl Seyfert), 13 Dec. (Mr. Jack Weber), 1950 (Box 2)
  - 10 Jan. (Dr. S.H. Knight; Dr. Fredrick C. Kruger; Mr. E.V. Murphree) 4 12 Jan. (Mrs. Madeline Pond), 17 Jan. (Dr. H.R. Aldrich; Mr. J.P.D. Hall; W.C. Russell Moscasin Co.), 19 Jan. (Mrs. Madeline Pond), 24 Jan. (Mr. J.P.D. Hull), 31 Jan. (Dr. Fredrick C. Kruger; Mrs. Madeline Pond), 7 March (Dr. R.S. Poor), 26 March (Dr. T.G. Andrews; Mr. W.A. Bell; Mrs. Madeline Pond; Dr. Sam Shoup), 11 April (Office of Naval Research; Dr. Russell S. Poor), 30 April (Office of Naval Reaearch), 4 May (Dr. Frank G. Snyder), 9 May (Dr. H.R. Aldrich; Dr. Frank G. Snyder), 17 May (Mr. W.A. Bell; Mrs. Madeline Pond), 24 May (Mr. H.R. Martin), 11 June (Dr. Charles W. Wilson, Jr.), 5 Oct. (Hr. Harris H. Allen; D.H. Delo; Hr. Stuart C. Dorman; Hr. Bianton C. Duncan; Hr. Bobby Floyd; Hr. W.D. Johns; Hrs. Madeline Pond; Mr. Warren Sullivan; Tenn. Hospital Service Assoc.), 31 Oct. (Mr. B.J. Floyd; Prof. Marcellus H. Stow), 27 Nov. (Hrs. Walter F. Pond), 6 Dec. (Hiss J. Hay Lynch), 1951 (Box 2)
  - 9 Jan. (Hrs. J.H. Gregg), 11 Jan. (SFC Hilford B. Gardner; Hr. A.E. Sayles; Tenn. Hosp. Service Assoc.), 16 Jan. (SFC Hilford B. Gardner), 23 Jan. (Evans Speciality Co., Inc.; Prof. B.F. Howell; Dr. Frederick Kruger; 7 Feb. (Hr. A.B. Benedict. Mr. H.R. Aldrich) 13 Feb. (Dr. O.C. Carmichael; SFC Milford ti. Gardner; Dr. Lyle Lanier; Mr. E.V. Murphree; Dp. John Pomfret; Prof. John Ransom; Prof. Randall Stewart), 22 Feb. (L.L. BearXi Inc.; xhomas Collators), 5 March (L.L. Bean; Mr. Laffitte; Secretary of the University, Princeton Univ.; Mr. Malcolm C. Shurtleff; Union Carbide and Carbon Corp.), 26 March (Dr. John £. Pomfret; Mrs. Madeline Pond; Dr. F.G. Snyder), 2 April (Mr. Blanton C. Duncan; Dr. Fredrick C. Kruger), 16 April (Multiplex Display Fixture Co.), 23 April (Denoyer-Geppert Co.; Mr. Bianton C. Duncan), 12 May (American Geological Inst.; Mr. Stuart C. fiorman ), 14 May (Dr. Joe Peoples), 5 June (Dr. H.fi. Aldrich; Mr. H.B. Northcutt), 23 Sept. (Mr. James Buford),. 26 Sept. (Mr. Stuart C. Dorraan; Mr. D.J. Jones; Mrs. J.S. Morrel), 1 Oct. (Mrs. E.F. Lamb; Mrs. Frances B. Peters; Dr. Francis Slack), 11 Oct. (Mr. David M. Baird; Mr. Frank E. Fahlquist; Mr. J.B. Murray), 16 Oct. (Lapidary Equipment Co.), 18 Oct. (Prof. Wlm A. Kelly), 30 Oct. (Prof. Wlm. A. Kelly), 6 Nov. (Mr. Herman Ferguson; Ward's Natural Science Establishment), 14 Nov. CProf. John H. Davis; Mr. Howard N. Sloane), 20 Nov. (Mr. & Mrs. W.B. Brown; Mr. G.H. Freyermuth - Std. Oil of N.J.; Mr. Wlm. E. Tanner), 5 Dec. (Prof. Josef Rysan), 6 Dec. (Prof. Donald Davidson; Mr. Herman Ferguson), 11 Dec. (Mr. C.E. Springhorn), 23 Dec. (Art Metal Const. Co.; Mr. Herman Ferguson; Prof. W.A. Kelly; Tenn. Valley Authority), 1952 (Box 2)
  - 29 Jan. (Griegers; Mr. John Haldi), 7 Feb. (Mr. George J. Podeyn; Hamil- ton Manufacturing Co.), 9 Eeb. (Mr. M. Segal), 12 Feb. (Sandia Corp), 14 Feb. (Abrams Instrument Corp.), 19 Feb. (Mr. Robt. A. Laurence), 23 Feb. (Bausch & Lomb Optical Co.; Bausch & Lomb Optical Co.; Mrs. McCary; Natl. Science Foundation), 26 Feb. (Miss Mary Fairbanks; Mr. Robert A. Laurence; Dr. Robert Shaver), 5 March (Mr. H.W. Ferguson; Mr. Hervie Hobbs), 12 March (Miss Gladys Hannaford), 26. March (Miss Gladys Babson Hannaford; Mr. J. May Lynch; Mr. James H. Stone), 31 March (Benjamin Franklin Press, Inc.; Oil Industry Information Committee), 6 April (Bausch & Lomb; Mrs. Madeline Pond), 11 April (Miss Minnie Willey), 14 April (Dr. F.C. Kruger), 16 April (Mr. Homer Bollinger), 27 April (Exec. Director - Newsletter - Amer. Geol. Inst.; 1st. Lt. Leverne E. Barnes, Jr.; Dr. Richard R. Priddy), 11 May (Bausch and Lomb Optical Co.; Dr. Francis Slack), l8 May (Mr. Jack Dowdy; Readers' Digest; Time Magazine), 19 May (Bausch and Lomb Optical Co.), 29 May (Mr. Frank S. Flores; Mr. Wayne L. Jeffers; Nashville Trust Co.), 8 Oct. (Mr. J. G0n- zalez-Reyna; Mr. D.W. Lackey; Mr. Benton Mc Keehan; Dr. Paris B. Stockdale; Mr. Thomas B. Temple; Mr. Pemberton B. Wall; Mrs. Carolyn Evins Willard; Mr. C Overton Williams), 13 Oct. (Pres. John T. Caldwell; Denoyer-Geppert Co.; Dean Nichols), 22 Oct. (Allied Radio; Dr. T.G. Andrews; Arizona Geol. Society; Burstein-Applebee Co.), 29 Oct. (Bausch & Lomb Optical Co.; The R.Y. Ferner Co., Inc.; Mr. John Haldi; Rand-McNally & Co.), 12 Nov. (Prof. J. Robert Berg; Dr. Richard M. Foose; Dr. Joe Webb Peoples; Students and Friends of Prof. L.C. ulenn), 19 Nov. (Dr. James S. Sullison; Dept. of Geology - Franklin and Marshall College; Jarrell-Ash Co.,; Keuffel and Esser), 3 Dec. (Allied Radio), 10 Dec. (Mr. Francis L. Haley; Miss Laura Louise Hart; Prof. Helen Stobbe), 1953 (Box 2)
  - 14 Jan. (Mr. C. Stratton Lindenmeyer; Lt. (j.g.) A.E. Niles; Pacific Museum; Mr. J.B. Pritchard; Mr. Jack Sheean;), 21 Jan. (Pres. John T. Caldwell - Univ. of Ark.; Natl. Science Foundation; Penn Fishing tackle Mfg. Co.; Dr. George Swingle), 28 Jan. (Prof. Curtis H. Walker), 4 Feb. (Prof. H.E. Eyeland), 11 Feb. (Mr. L.L. Bean; Mr. James "onley; Hr. David A. Ogden), l8 Feb. (Mr. Boy Davis; Prof. J.J. Galloway; Herbach & Rademan, Inc.; Dr. Francis G. Slack), 30 March C.S. Hammond & Co.; Mr. Wlm. M. Hinson; Prof. B.F. Howell; Dr. H.K. Stephenson; A/2c Lloyd Dean), 23 April (Mr. E.E. Bryan; Mr. Robt. Hershey), 26 April (Dr. Harold N. Fish; Mr. Frank Flores; Mr. Stratton Lindenmayer; Dr. Francis G. Slack), 6 May (Dr. Harold N. Fisk; Mr. Alan E. Sayles), 17 May (Dr. John T. Bate; Dr. Harold N. Fisk; Dr. R. H. Purdy; Time, Inc.), 20 May (Dr. Clarke; Mr. Herman Fer-guson; Mr. Robt. A. Laurence; Dr. Charles -H.L. Oder), 4 June (Nash-ville Trust Co.; 7 June (Donald Lee Hay;), 8 June (Mr. Hann ), 28 Oct. (Mr. Charles Coleman; Lapidary Equip. Co.), 17 Nov. (Mr. Ben E. Clement; Mr. CharloB Coleman; Mrs. Oliver Cunningham; Mr. Lloyd N. Dnsell; Mr. Stratton Lindenmeyer; Dr. Joe Webb Peoples; Mrs. Grace Phelps), 13 Dec. (Mr. Ben Clement; Gurley & Co.; Mr. Richard Kovacs; Dr. Vincent E. Nelson; Mr. Ralph Nichols; Mr. Mike Rea; Chas. Weidinger Co.) 18 March (Specialities Mfg. Co., Inc. ), 1954 (Box 2)
  - 7 Jan. (Mr. Berlin C. Moneymaker;)31 Jan. (Mr. Berlin C. Moneymaker; Mrs. Grace Phelps), 3 Feb. (Buehler, Ltd.; Mr. Charles Coleman; Mr. Herman Ferguson; Mr. Stratton Lindenmeyer; Chas. Weidinger Co.,) 15 Feb. (Mrs. Hazel Born), 21 Feb. (Buehler, Ltd.; Mr. Sarles Coleman; Mr. M.W. Avery; Department W., Life; A.J. Nystron & Co.; Mr. J.W. Wolfram - Oldsmobile Div.), 24 Feb. (Griegers; Paul R. Flanigan Mfg. Co.; Pacific Museum; Specialities Mfg. Co.), 8 March (Miss Eliza Hennessey; Mr. J.S. McLaughlin; Dr. Lawrence Whitcomb), 14 March (Mr. Hobt. G. Campbell), 22 March (Dr. J.G. Lester), 30 March (Mr. David C. Miller; Mr. Jake Nicholson; Mr. Kalph T. Overman;), 4 April (Mr. Clement), l8 April (American Optical Co.; Bell and Howell Co.; General Electric Co.; Dean Fred J. Lewis; Mr. Bryant Mather; Obsolete Tire C0.), 26 April (X'he Flanigan Manufacturing Co.; Mr. Jake Hicholson;) 16 May (Dr. G.H. Crowl; Mr. Wade Roark), 17 May (Time, Inc.), 31 May (Mr. ""lenient; Mr. Eugene Curtiss; Mr. John W. Taylor; Wilson Truck °o.) 28 June (Mr. Lytle Brown), 30 Sept. (Mr. Lytle Brown; Prof. H.C. Nixon; Mr. Bailey Rascoe, Jr.; Wilson Truck Co.), 21 Oct. (Mr. John Grieger - Grieger's Inc.; Mr. J.G. Lester; Mr. Frank N. Schluntz), 2 Nov. (Dean Nora C. Chaffin; Frank L. Howard Eigineering Co.), 16 "ov. (Mr. H.H. Clark - Wilson Truck Co.), 30 Nov. (Prof. Wm. R. Evltt; Mrs. Tony Hose; Mr. Overton Williams), 7 Dec. (Mrs. Eunice Thomas Miner), 1955 (Box 2)
  - 7 Jan. (Mr. Potts), 9 Jan. (Dean John L. Bingham), 11 Jan. (Mr. Gardner Beehr; Prof. Edgar Bowles; Mr. Jim Buford), 24 Jan. (Mr. Morris Burgess; Miss Eera Stevens), 26 Jan. (Warren Coolidge ?), 1 Eeb. (Consider H. Wilmette °o.), 15 Feb. (Cadet Carlton White), 5 March (Prof. Wm. M. Merrill), 19 March (Mr. John W. Jewell), 2 April (Mr. H.C. Potts), 4 April (E. Leitz, Inc.), ... 18 April (Office of the Secretary - Pacific Lighting Corp.; Dr. George W. Stocking), 24 April (Pvt. Loarain Giddings, Jr.; Mr. John H. Hutchison; Mr. Peter A. Morrell), l8 May (Mrs. John W. Jewell; Dr. A.K. Snelgrove), 4 June (Mr. Pembroke J. Hart), 30 July (Mr. Pembroke J. Hart), 11 Sept. (Mr. Paul Oakley), 4 Oct. (Dr. Amos Christie; Mr. Leland F. Grant), 5 Oct. (Dr. Jamed W. Clarke; ML. C. Jackson Davis; The Evinrude Motors; Mr. E.B. Pilcher), 25 Oct. (Mr. L.R. Stannard - Evinrude Motors), 26 Oct. (Miss Emma Lila Fundaburk; Mrs. Frances Gross; Mr. E.B. Pilcher; Mr. Russ Spedden; Miss Jane Sutherland; The Vanderbilt Hustler), 2 Nov. (Herbert Weaver), 20 Nov. (Evinrude Motors), 1956 (Box 2)
  - 4 Jan. (A.B. Dick Co.; Miss Emma Lila Fundaburk; Dr. F.G. Snyder), 11 Jan. (Prof. Norman S. Hinchey), 23 Jan. (Miss Emma Lila Fundaburk; Mrs. Franklin H. Pond), l8 Feb. (Lt. j.g. John M. Colvin, Jr.), 19 Feb. (Mr. Roy W. Cole) Prof. Shirley A. Lynch; Mr. Berlen C. Moneymaker), 18 March (Mr. Ben E. Clement), 18 April (Educational Division - Amer. Paulin System; Mr. E.p. Erickson; Mrs. Ethel Sayles), 30 April (Prof. David B. Camp; Lt. d,.g. John M. Colvin, Jr.), 7 May (Mr. Hubbard), 30 May (Mr. C. Jackson Davis), 19 Sept. (Mr. Ben E. Clement; Mr. Russell P. MacFall; Mr. Norman A. Hemes), 16 Oct. (Dr. H.R. Aldrich; Mr. Cobert Brown), 7 Nov. (Mr. Richard P. Shull), 20 Nov. (Dr. James E. Clarke), 18 Dec. (Mr. Here Alley; Prof. J.E. Gill; Prof. Alonzo W. Quinn; Mrs. Audie Renfro; Miss Emma Lila Fundaburk), 19 Dec. (Prof. Arthur L. Howland; Dr. A.W. Ingersoll), 1957 (Box 2)
  - 10 Jan. (Mrs. Otto Renfro; Dr. Francis G. Slack), 12 Feb. (Bureau of Mines; General Binding Corp; Mr. Berlen C. Moneymaker; Prof. Joe W. Peoples; Prof. O.F. Tuttle), 24 Feb. (Prof. Harry Klepser), 3 March (American Geological Inst.; Dr. Pembroke Hart), 4 March (Mr. Tom Hardy; Dean Leon F. Sensabaugh - Wash. & Lee Univ.), 13 harch (Miss Virginia Soderling; Mr. T.T. Hardy; Prof. Joe Webb Peoples), 8 April (Miss "irginia °oderling), 11 April (American Geological Inst.), 14 April (Senator Gordon Allott; Mr. C.C. Campen; Dr. Pembroke Hart; Mr. Lyal Sands), 16 April (Mr. T.H. Hardy), 18 April (Miss Virginia R. Sonderling; Prof. Joe W. Peoples), 25 April (Dr. R.R. Priddy), 14 May ( Prof. E.C. Abendanon; Prof. Chas. H. Behre, Jr.; Hamilton Watch Co.; Mrs. Franklin H. Pond; Dr. °.£. Prouty; Time, Inc.), 24 Sept. (Mr. Nat Dortch; 26 S«pt. (Mr. Nat Dortch; Dr. Alex Dragnich; Prof. Auguste Mailloux; Mrs. Carolyn McCary; Mr. Frank A. Rikard; Dr. Dan M. Robinson), 29 Sept. (Mr. O.J. Lynch; 15 Oct. (Mr. Nat Dortch; Mr. Robert McGaw), 29 Oct. (Hamilton Watch Co.; Dr. Pem Hart; Mr. EveretteE. Kelley} Prof, alonzo W. Quinn), 19 Nov. (Mr. J.W. Wolfram), 28 Nov. (Mr. Paul J. Kuhn Prof. H. Craig Sipe), 3 Dec. (Council of Southern Univs., toe), 12 Dec. (Fossil Supply Co.; Prof. Alonzo W. Quinn), 1958 (Box 2)
  - 27 Jan. (Mr. Gholam Sorrwar; Treasury Dept; Prof. F.A. Welder; John Wiley 6 Sons, Inc.), 24 Feb. (Mr. P.J. Hart), 10 March (Mr. Charles McCary), 11 March (Mining and Petrol. Committee - Colorado St. Chamber of Commerce; Mr. J.M. Colvin; Ensign T.E. Oden), 31 March (Siade, Hipp and Meloy), 7 April (M/Sgt. Vincent Frazier; Mr. E.O. Nimmer), 14 April (Edward Swaim and Co.), 7 May (Dr. Pembroke Hart), 26 May (Mr. Harry Cantey; Dr. Thomas M.N. Lewis), 8 Oct. (Dr. James Clarke; SP/k Edmund B. Corley, II; Dr. P,J. Hart; Prof. Jim Lester; Dr. John Lucke; Dr. Joe Peoples; Mr. M. Segal), 28 Oct. (Mr. Marshall G. Frazer), 6 Nov. (Mr. M. Segal), 11 Nov. (Evinrude Motors; The Honor Council), 21 Dec. (Robert L. Wilson), 1959 (Box 2)
  - 25 Jan. (Dr. Joe Webb Peoples; Mr. H.C. Potts; Dr. Sam Shoup; Smithsonian Inst.), 29 Jan. (Mr. M.B.S. Giri), 2 Feb. (Mr. Michael C. Schneider), 30 March (The Geographical Press; Mr. Lars E. Persson; Mr. Stephen Stow), 13 April (Mr. Lars Persson), 11 May (Mr. B.E. Clement; Saturday Evening Post; Mrs. W.L. Settlemire; Mr. Steve Stow), 1960 (Box 2)
  - (Mrs. Ralph Mitchell; American Geological Inst.), n.d. (Box 2)
  - no addressee -- 2, and 1 fragment (Box 2)
- This list includes letters written to W.B. Jewell, with the exception of letters categorised by subject, a listing of which follows the incoming correspondence list.
  - Abrams Instrument Corp., 1947; 2 (Box 3)
  - The Academy of Natl. Sciences, 1947; 1 (Box 3)
  - Aero Service Crop., 1954; 1 (Box 3)
  - Alexander, Frank, 1942-53 & n.d.; 8 (Box 3)
  - Allott, Gordon, 1958; 1 (Box 3)
    U.S. Senator
  - The American Aasoc. of Petrol. Geologists, 1947-58; 2 (Box 3)
  - American Comm. for Emigre Scholars, Writers etc., 1954; 1 (Box 3)
  - American Geographical Soc., 1943; 1 (Box 3)
  - American Geological Inst., 1949-58; 9 (Box 3)
  - Amer. Inst, of Geonomy, 1957; l (Box 3)
  - Amer. Inst, of Mining, 1939-59; 4 (Box 3)
  - Amer. Museum of Natl. History, 1951; l (Box 3)
  - American Optical Co., 1955; l (Box 3)
  - American Petroleum Inst., n.d.; l (Box 3)
  - The American University, 1955; 1 (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Betty, 1947; l (Box 3)
  - Anderson, H.O., 1947; 1 (Box 3)
  - Anderson, W.J., 1945; 1 (Box 3)
  - Andrews, T.G., 1934-51; 7 (Box 3)
  - Andrew Technical Service, 1947; 4 (Box 3)
  - Anglia, Byron, 1942; 4 (Box 3)
  - Appleton-Centmry Co., Inc., 1943; 1 (Box 3)
  - Assoc. of Geology Teachers, 1955-58; 2 (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Oak Flooring Co., 1948; 2 (Box 3)
  - The Atlantic Refining Co., 1944-48; 2 (Box 3)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1947; 1 (Box 3)
  - Avery, Hilton, 1946; 1 (Box 3)
  - Ayer, N.W. & Son, 1953; 2 (Box 3)
  - Babbitt, Samuel F., 1957; 1 (Box 3)
    V.U. Dean of Men
  - Barnes, Leverne F., Jr., 1953; 1 (Box 3)
  - Barr, Thomas C, Jr., 1950 & n.d.; 2 (Box 3)
  - Bate, John T., 1949-54; 3 (Box 3)
  - Bausch & Lomb Optical Co., 1928-53; 8 (Box 3)
  - Bean, L.L., Inc., 1950-52; 2 (Box 3)
  - Beatty, Richmond C., 1 (Box 3)
  - Beehr, Jardner, 1956; 1 (Box 3)
  - Behre, Chas. H., 1939-58; 7 (Box 3)
  - Bell & Howell Co., 1941-55; 2 (Box 3)
  - Benedict, A.B., 1942-52; 5 (Box 3)
    V.U. Treasurer
  - Benedict, A.B. (Mrs.), n.d.; 1 (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Kelley E., 1949; 1 (Box 3)
  - Bergmann, Theo, Shoe Manuf., 1937; 1 (Box 3)
  - Berlin Glove Co., 1937; 1 (Box 3)
  - Berryhill, Louise Russell, 1948; 1 (Box 3)
  - Bingham, John L., 1957; 1 (Box 3)
    Asst. Dean - V.U. Arts & Scs.
  - Bircher, Louis J., 1951-56; 2 (Box 3)
  - Birdsong, Troy L., 1950; 1 (Box 3)
  - Blevins, Wm. A., 1943; 1 (Box 3)
  - Blue Goose Hotel, 1959; 1 (Box 3)
  - Bold, Harold C., 1953-54; 2 (Box 3)
  - Bollinger, Homer, 1953; 2 (Box 3)
  - Bookstore (V.U.), 1953; 1 (Box 3)
  - Born, Kendall E., 1932-47; 2 (Box 3)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, 1956; 1 (Box 3)
  - The Brier Hill Collieries, 1928; 1 (Box 3)
  - Brown, Betty, 1952; 1 (Box 3)
  - Brown, Lytle, 1955; 1 (Box 3)
  - Brown, O.E., 1931; 1 (Box 3)
  - The Brown Univ. Alumni Fund, 1943-48 & n.d.'s; 4 (Box 3)
  - Brown, Wes, 1942-52; 3 (Box 3)
  - Bryan, E.E., 1931-54 & n.d.; 13 (Box 3)
    V.U. Dept. of Bldgs.
  - Buddington, A.F., 1929-51 & n.d.; 10 (Box 3)
  - Buehler Ltd., 1955; 1 (Box 3)
  - Buford, James L., 1945-58; 2 (Box 3)
    V.U. Director of Admissions & Univ. Registrar
  - Burchard, E.F., 1932-42; 5 (Box 3)
    Geological Survey
  - Caldwell, John T., 1953-54; 3 (Box 3)
    Pres. - Univ. of Alabama
  - Cambe Log Library, 1946; 1 (Box 3)
  - Camp, David h., 1957; 2 (Box 3)
  - Campbell, Robert G., 1955 & n.d.; 3 (Box 3)
  - Canada Dept. of Mines & Technical Surveys, 1951; 2 (Box 3)
  - Gantey, Harry, 1959; 1 (Box 3)
  - Carman, J. Ernest, 1934; 2 (Box 3)
    Dept. of Geology - Ohio St. U
  - Carmichael, Oliver C, Jr., 1956; 1 (Box 3)
    V.U. Dev. Foundation
  - Carpenter, George K., 1947; 1 (Box 3)
  - The Carter Oil Co., 1942-56; 3 (Box 3)
  - Central Bus Lines, Inc., 1947-48; 5 (Box 3)
  - Central Scientific Co., 1941-43; 3 (Box 3)
  - The Chemical Rubber Co., 1949; 1 (Box 3)
  - Chaffin, Nora C., 1944-56; 6 (Box 3)
    Dean of Women - V.U.
  - Chang, Sukyoon, 1942; 1 (Box 3)
  - Chemical & Engineering News, 1945; 1 (Box 3)
  - Cincinnati, Univ. of, 1944; 1 (Box 3)
    (Dept. of Geol. & Geogr)
  - Clarke, James W., 1950-57 & n.d.; 4 (Box 3)
  - Clement, B.E., 1954-60; 7 (Box 3)
  - Cole, Roy W., 1953-57; 3 (Box 3)
  - Coleman, Charles, 1955; 3 (Box 3)
  - Colgate University, 1948; 3 (Box 3)
  - Colorado State Chamber of Comm., 1959; 1 (Box 3)
  - Colvin, John M., Jr., 1957-59; 3 (Box 3)
  - Commercial Letter Shop, 1950; 1 (Box 3)
  - Conley, James, 1954; l (Box 3)
  - Cooksey, Lindon T., 1943; 1 (Box 3)
  - Corbett, M. Everett, 1948; 1 (Box 3)
  - Corley, Edmund B. II, 1959; l (Box 3)
  - Council of Southern Univs., Inc., 1958; 1 (Box 3)
  - Crawford, Meredith P., (4); 1947-49 (Box 3)
    Dean - V.U. Junior College
  - Crowl, Ceorge H., 1942-55; 14 (Box 3)
  - Crucible Club, 1942; 1 (Box 3)
  - Cullison, James S., 1953; 2 (Box 3)
    Dept. of aeol. - F.S.U.
  - Cumberland Caverns, 1959; 1 (Box 3)
  - W.H. Curtin & Co., 1948; 1 (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Oliver (Mrs.), 1954; 1 (Box 3)
  - Curtiss, Eugene, 1950 & n.d.; 2 (Box 3)
  - Darby, William J., 1952; 1 (Box 3)
    Depts. of Med. & Biochem. (V.U)
  - Davidson, Donald, 1952; 1 (Box 3)
  - D.T. Davis Co., 1947; 1 (Box 3)
  - Davis, C. Jackson, 1956-57; 2 (Box 3)
  - Davis, John H., 1952; 1 (Box 3)
    Rhodes Scholarship Committee
  - Dravis, Roy Tasco, 1948; 1 (Box 3)
    Inter-American Schools Service
  - Davis, Roy, 1953-54; 2 (Box 3)
    Nashville Crotto
  - Denoyer-Geppert Co., 1941-59; 1 (Box 3)
  - A.B. Dick Co., 1957; 1 (Box 3)
  - Dietrich, H.V., 1960; 1 (Box 3)
  - Dortch, Nat, 1958; 3 (Box 3)
  - Dowdy, N., 1953; 1 (Box 3)
  - Duncan, Blanton C., 1951-52; 3 (Box 3)
  - E.P. Button & Co., Inc., 1943; 1 (Box 3)
  - Eastman, Joseph B., 1942; 1 (Box 3)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1943-48; 6 (Box 3)
  - Educators Visual-Aid Service, 1947 and n.d.; 2 (Box 3)
  - The Electrochemical Society, Inc., 1942; 1 (Box 3)
  - Emory University, 1950 and n.d.; 2 (Box 3)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica Films, 1944; 1 (Box 3)
  - Erpi Classroom Films, 1943-; 5 (Box 3)
  - Estwing Manufacturing Co., 1934-45; 3 (Box 3)
  - Eveland, H.E., 1 (Box 3)
    Lamar St. College of Tech. (1954)
  - Eversharp, Inc., 1941; 1 (Box 3)
  - Evinrude Motors, 1956-59; 2 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Tailoring Co., 1934; 2 (Box 3)
  - Fahlquist, Frank E., 1952; 2 (Box 3)
  - Fairchild Camera & Instrum., 1953; 1 (Box 3)
  - Farrar, R. Lynn, Jr., 1945-46; 3 (Box 3)
  - Farrell, Joanne, 1943; l (Box 3)
  - Ferguson, Herman W., 1943-55 & n.d.'s; 4 (Box 3)
  - Field, Richard W., 1927; 1 (Box 3)
  - Fields, Emmett B., 1957; 1 (Box 3)
    Director of Summer Session (V
  - Films of Commerce Co., 1944; 2 (Box 3)
  - Fishel, W.P., 1953; 1 (Box 3)
  - Fisher, Jno. T., 1956; 1 (Box 3)
  - Paul R. Flanigan Mfg. Co., 1954-55; 4 (Box 4)
  - Flint, George M., 1946-; 2 (Box 4)
  - Flint, George M., Jr., 1931; 1 (Box 4)
  - Flores, Frank, 1953-54; 3 (Box 4)
  - Floyd, B.J., 1951-52; 3 (Box 4)
  - Foose, Richard M., 1953; 1 (Box 4)
    Dept. of Geol. - Franklin & Marshall College
  - Ford, William L. III, 1955; 1 (Box 4)
  - Fossill Supply Co., 1958; 1 (Box 4)
  - Franklin Limestone Co., 1942; 1 (Box 4)
  - Frazer, Marshall G., 1959; 1 (Box 4)
  - Frazier, Vincent, 1959; 1 (Box 4)
  - Fundaburk, Emma Lila, 1956-57; 5 (Box 4)
  - Galloway, J.J.9, 1954; 1 (Box 4)
    Dept. of Geol. - Indiana Univ.
  - Gamma Scientific Co., 1949; 1 (Box 4)
  - Garden St. Minerals, n.d.; 1 (Box 4)
  - Gardner, Ballard, 1951-52; 3 (Box 4)
  - Gardner, Edwin S., 1944-61; 2 (Box 4)
    Bursar, Treasurer - V.U.
  - GBC Sales & Service, 1958; 1 (Box 4)
  - Gem Hunter's Guide, 1957; 1 (Box 4)